PRANSHU KUMAR

Student

My Contact

+91 6209207993

Darbhanga,Bihar-846009

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pr anshu-kumar-512a41215

Skills

- Java, Python
- DSA
- OOPs
- DBMS
- SQL
- · Html, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- UI/UX
- Probem solving Skills
- Leadership Skill

Education Background

08/2021 - Current
 Vellore Institute Of Technology | Vellore, TN
 B.Tech: Computer Science
 Specialization in Bioinformatics
 CGPA: 8.63

06/2019-06/2021
 Public School Darbhanga | Darbhanga, BR
 Higher Secondary: Science - PCM
 Grade: A

 03/2007-04/2019
 Madonna English School | Darbhanga, BR Secondary
 Grade: A

Hobbies

- Chess
- Cricket
- Reading Books

About Me

I am currently pursuing my B. Tech in Computer Science from Vellore Institute of Technology, with a specialization in Bioinformatics. I am actively utilizing my technical and analytical skills to increase my knowledge in the field. I am working hard to gain the maximum benefit from this program, and I am confident that my studies will help me achieve success in the future.

Experience

03/2022-Current

Senior core member

Mozilla Firefox club | VIT Vellore, India

- · Design Domain
- Coordinated activities and communicated information among the board, external auditors and management.

03/2022-Current
Senior core member
IEEE EMBS Chapter | VIT Vellore, India

- Design And Management Domains
- Coordinated activities and communicated information among the board, external auditors and management.

03/2022-Current
Senior Core Member

IETE Chapter | VIT Vellore, IndiaTechnical Domains

02/2023-03/2023 Social Worker Hamari Pahachan NGO | New Delhi, India

03/2022-04/2022 Campus Ambassador IIT Delhi | New Delhi, India

Achievements

- 5 star C, C++, Java and Python coder on HackerRank
- Gold Medalist in Forest and their management course by IIT Kanpur

Certifications

- Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS.
- Python for Machine Language
- · Leadership skills from IIM Ahmedabad